http://www.intexts.com/privacy-policy/

ServicesLanguage ServicesIndustry-specific translationMultilingual desktop publishingMachine translationMultimedia localizationSoftware localizationInterpretingTranscreationTerminology managementTranslation quality assessmentMarketing ServicesBranding and rebrandingContent creationEvent servicesGraphic designSocial mediaOnline broadcastingTrade show supportPhotographyVideo productionOutstaffingLanguagesArmenianAzeriBelarusianBosnianBulgarianCroatianEnglishFrenchGeorgianGermanHungarianItalianKazakhMacedonianPolishRomanianRussianSerbianSpanishUkrainianUzbekAbout UsThe companyOur historyOur teamLibraryCareersBlogUTICampContacts
ServicesLanguage ServicesIndustry-specific translationMultilingual desktop publishingMachine translationMultimedia localizationSoftware localizationInterpretingTranscreationTerminology managementTranslation quality assessmentMarketing ServicesBranding and rebrandingContent creationEvent servicesGraphic designSocial mediaOnline broadcastingTrade show supportPhotographyVideo productionOutstaffingLanguagesArmenianAzeriBelarusianBosnianBulgarianCroatianEnglishFrenchGeorgianGermanHungarianItalianKazakhMacedonianPolishRomanianRussianSerbianSpanishUkrainianUzbekAbout UsThe companyOur historyOur teamLibraryCareersBlogUTICampContacts
Contact Us
Get a Quote
Language ServicesIndustry-specific translationMultilingual desktop publishingMachine translationMultimedia localizationSoftware localizationInterpretingTranscreationTerminology managementTranslation quality assessmentMarketing ServicesBranding and rebrandingContent creationEvent servicesGraphic designSocial mediaOnline broadcastingTrade show supportPhotographyVideo productionOutstaffing
Main
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
InText (“we,” “our,” or “us”) is committed to protecting your privacy.  This Privacy Policy explains how your personal information is collected, used, and disclosed by InText.
This Privacy Policy applies to our website, and its associated subdomains (collectively, our “Service”) alongside our application, InText. By accessing or using our Service, you signify that you have read, understood, and agree to our collection, storage, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service.
Meanings
For this Privacy Policy:
You is referred to the person who accessed the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.
Company (referred to as either "the Company", "We", "Us" or "Our" in this Agreement) refers to InText.
Website is referred to InText.
Service is referred to the website.
Service Provider means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Company. It refers to third-party companies or individuals employed by the Company to facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on behalf of the Company, to perform services related to the Service or to assist the Company in analyzing how the Service is used.
Third-party Social Media Service could be any website or social network website in which a User can log in or create an account to use the Service.
Personal Data is any information that relates to an identified or identifiable individual.
Cookies are a small amount of data generated by a website and saved by your web browser. Its purpose is to remember information about you, similar to a preference file created by a software application.
Device could be any device with internet who can access the service such as a mobile phone, a computer or a digital tablet.
Usage Data it’s referred to the data that’s been collected automatically, either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself. For example, how many times the user accessed the website.
What Information Do We Collect?
We collect information from you when you visit our website, register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.
Email address
Name / username
How Do We Use The Information We Collect?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emails
How Do We Use Your Email Address?
By submitting your email address on this website, you agree to receive emails from us. You can cancel your participation in any of these email lists at any time by clicking on the opt-out link or other unsubscribe option that is included in the respective email. We only send emails to people who have authorized us to contact them, either directly, or through a third party. We do not send unsolicited commercial emails, because we hate spam as much as you do. By submitting your email address, you also agree to allow us to use your email address for customer audience targeting on sites like Facebook, where we display custom advertising to specific people who have opted-in to receive communications from us. IIf you have provided your email to us through any method, we may use it for any of the purposes stated in this Policy. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How Long Do We Keep Your Information?
We keep your information only so long as we need it to provide InText services to you and fulfill the purposes described in this policy. This is also the case for anyone that we share your information with and who carries out services on our behalf. When we no longer need to use your information and there is no need for us to keep it to comply with our legal or regulatory obligations, we’ll either remove it from our systems or depersonalize it so that we can't identify you.
How Do We Protect Your Information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place a quote or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the absolute security of any information you transmit to InText or guarantee that your information on the Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by a breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.
Your Consent
By using our site, registering a quote, and leaving your email, you consent to this Privacy Policy.
Links to Other Websites
Our service may contain links to other websites that are not operated by Us. If You click on a third party link, You will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise You to review the Privacy Policy of every site You visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Cookies for Advertising
Cookies help to make advertising more effective. Without cookies, it’s really hard for an advertiser to reach its audience, or to know how many ads were shown and how many clicks they received.
Cookies
InText uses "Cookies" to identify the areas of our website that you have visited. A Cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser. We use Cookies to personalize the Content that you see on our website. Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies. However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to access functionality on our website correctly or at all. We never place Personally Identifiable Information in Cookies.
Remarketing Services
We use remarketing services. What Is Remarketing? In digital marketing, remarketing (or retargeting) is the practice of serving ads across the internet to people who have already visited your website. It allows your company to seem like they're “following” people around the internet by serving ads on the websites and platforms they use most.
Kids' Privacy
We do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If You are a parent or guardian and You are aware that Your child has provided Us with Personal Data, please contact Us. If We become aware that We have collected Personal Data from anyone under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, We take steps to remove that information from Our servers.
Changes To Our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
Third-Party Services
We may display, include or make available third-party content (including data, information, applications and other products services) or provide links to third-party websites or services ("Third- Party Services").
You acknowledge and agree that InText shall not be responsible for any Third-Party Services, including their accuracy, completeness, timeliness, validity, copyright compliance, legality, decency, quality or any other aspect thereof. InText Translation Solutions OÜ does not assume and shall not have any liability or responsibility to you or any other person or entity for any Third-Party Services.
Third-Party Services and links thereto are provided solely as a convenience to you and you access and use them entirely at your own risk and subject to such third parties' terms and conditions.
Information Regarding Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your personal information.
If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), our legal basis for collecting and using your personal information, as described in this Privacy Policy, depends on the information we collect and the specific context in which we collect it. We may process your personal information because:
We need to perform a contract with you, such as when you use our services
You have given us permission to do so
The processing is in our legitimate interests and it's not overridden by your rights
To comply with the law
If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:
The right to access, update or to delete the personal information we have on you
The right of rectification
The right to object
The right of restriction
The right to data portability
The right to withdraw consent
Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.
You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).
California Residents
The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) requires us to disclose categories of Personal Information we collect and how we use it, the categories of sources from whom we collect Personal Information, and the third parties with whom we share it, which we have explained above.
We are also required to communicate information about rights California residents have under California law. You may exercise the following rights:
Right to Know and Access. You may submit a verifiable request for information regarding the: (1) categories of Personal Information we collect, use, or share; (2) purposes for which categories of Personal Information are collected or used by us; (3) categories of sources from which we collect Personal Information; and (4) specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you.
Right to Equal Service. We will not discriminate against you if you exercise your privacy rights.
Right to Delete. You may submit a verifiable request to close your account and we will delete Personal Information about you that we have collected.
Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.
If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.
We do not sell the Personal Information of our users.
For more information about these rights, please contact us.
Contact Us
Don't hesitate to contact us if you have any questions:  info@intext.eu
Working with InText is easy!
Get a Quote
We are using cookies to provide statistics that help us give you the best experience of our site, products and services. You can manage your settings and read more about our privacy policy.
Accept
Decline
Read more
